# CHRISTOPHER KSIAZAK

## PROJECT COORDINATOR

## **SUMMARY**

I'm Chris, a developer born and raised in El Paso, TX. I enjoy learning new technologies and applying that knowledge in designing and creating web applications. Currently, I am a Project Coordinator at C3i Solutions. I work in collaboration with our client, Castlight Health. Before, I attended the University of Texas at El Paso (UTEP) to study Electrical Engineering. At some point during this time, I realized that it wasn't a topic that I enjoyed. I joined the Full Stack Web Development program at Lambda School, which aided me in discovering my passion for tech and design.

## **CONTACT**

□ cksiazak@gmail.com

ksiazak.dev

**(**915) 253-8705

**♀** El Paso, Texas

**y** cksiazak\_dev

in cksiazak

**O** cksiazak

## **EDUCATION**

Lambda School · Apr. 2019 to Current

## **SKILLS**

**WEB DEVELOPMENT:** HTML5, CSS (LESS/SASS), Javascript, React, Redux, Node/Express, SQL

## **PROJECTS**

#### Ksiazak.dev

My personal portfolio page. The front end is built using Gatsby. I also created an API using Node/Express that will output my data JSON formatted. You may send a GET request to https://api.ksiazak.dev for the JSON output.

#### SongSight

SongSight allows you to select from a list of songs, save that song, or return similar songs based on dance-ability, key, and other metrics from our Data Science teams flask app. This was part 3 of our build week projects at Lambda school. I worked with 3 other React developers in planning out the application layout and function, as well as with our back-end developer and data science team.

#### SIXR

SIXR is a project creation and investment piece. This allows you to either find a project to invest in, or create a new project for others to select from.

I was paired up with another React developer, as well as a UI designer. I created the login, sign up, and project list pages to the (near) pixel perfect design that our designer had for us. Full functionality isn't complete yet, but I am planning on a rebuilding for full functionality.

#### DevDesk

We built a 'marketing page' for DevDesk. This was our first build week project utilizing HTML, CSS (with LESS), and vanilla JavaScript. I worked with another front-end developer, and I created the Home and Solutions pages.

## **EMPLOYMENT**

## C3i Solutions

El Paso, TX

Project Coordinator Mar. 2017 to Current

I joined C3i solutions in March of 2017, starting off as a support representative for our client Castlight Health. I assisted in developing our program from a support oriented role into a more technical one. As we transitioned through several product launches, I assisted in knowledge base development, processing reporting checks via Salesforce and JIRA, and reviewing/triaging support incidents. At the moment, I assist in maintaining the client's relationship with Anthem by overseeing support requests, analyzing flat files, and API requests.

## **Best Buy**

El Paso, Texas

Samsung Sales Associate · June 2014 to Mar. 2015

At Best Buy, I strove to meet sales goals by listening to the customer's needs, wants, and desires, then using that information, I was able to provide a total solution based on my product knowledge. I was promoted from a regular home theater consultant to a Samsung representative. This granted me the opportunity to provide Samsung specific training and ensuring our premium displays were organized and up to date. I departed to focus on school full time.

#### Sears

El Paso, Texas

Sales Consultant Aug. 2013 to Apr. 2014

At Sears, I regularly met sales and customer experience goals within the mattress department. Once again, this was achieved by asking open ended questions to better understand the customer's problems. I would pair them up with a product that would suit those needs, which in turn not only made the customer happy, but also reduced returns and exchanges. Before leaving, I was able to lead the department's product refresh.